domestically-speaking.com 2018-02-02

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Welcome to Domestically Speaking
Domestically Speaking has created this Privacy Policy in order to set forth the principles
governing our information-gathering and dissemination practices, including but not limited to
such activities as forums, chat rooms, personal profile pages, product reviews, article
commentary, blogs, RSS feeds and newsletters, among other offerings. Domestically Speaking
has a strong commitment to the privacy of our users. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies
only to information collected through Domestically Speaking and not to information collected
offline or to information you may provide to any third-party sites to which Domestically
Speaking may link, except as expressly provided herein.
Information We Collect
There are two kinds of information that Domestically Speaking can obtain about you:
“Anonymous Information” and “Personally Identifiable Information.”
“Anonymous Information” consists of non-personally-identifiable data, such as your Internet
Protocol (“IP”) address or domain, or information about your usage on Domestically Speaking
that is used for administrative purposes only. For example, an IP address is a unique string of
numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. Web servers
automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We may collect our users’ IP addresses
for such purposes as to help diagnose problems with our servers and to report aggregate
information to our advertisers, corporate affiliates and consultants, and to third parties that
perform particular services on our behalf.
We may also use the information linked to IP addresses to ban users who violate our Terms and
Conditions of use.
“Personally Identifiable Information” is any information that personally identifies you, such as
your name, street address, email address, or telephone number. We collect such information
when, for example, you enter a contest, subscribe to our email newsletter, and participate in other
interactive online activities such as forums.
When we collect Personally Identifiable Information from you, you will have the opportunity to
“opt in” to receive email or other digital communications from us and/or our business partners.
If you have submitted your personal information to Domestically Speaking, you may correct,
amend or delete the Personally Identifiable Information maintained on file about you if it is
incorrect.
In all cases, we will only use your information as permitted by law. Notwithstanding any other
provision of this Privacy Policy, however, we may disclose Personally Identifiable Information to
others if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary
to (a) comply with the law or with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights and property;
(c) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site; or (d) protect the personal safety or
property of our users or the public. Please note that we may not provide you with notice prior to
disclosure in such cases.

Use of “Cookies”
Domestically Speaking uses “cookies” – data that is transferred from Domestically Speaking to
your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your
interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit
Domestically Speaking. Some of the advertisements appearing on Domestically Speaking are
delivered by our third-party ad network, DoubleClick. In the course of serving advertisements,
DoubleClick may place or recognize a unique “cookie” in your browser’s cache, and may use
Anonymous Information (including date/time of the banner ad displayed, the ad that was
displayed and the IP address of the visitor) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order
to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you and to collect statistical
information. For more information about DoubleClick’s privacy policy, please click here. If you
would like to “opt out” of having a unique cookie placed on your hard drive by DoubleClick,
please click here or here.
Disclosure of Information through Business Transfers
As we continue to develop our business, we may buy, merge or partner with other companies or
businesses, and in so doing, acquire customer information. In such transactions, user information
may be among the transferred assets. Similarly, in the event that a portion or all of Domestically
Speaking’s assets are sold or transferred to a third party, customer information (including your
email address) would likely be one of the transferred business assets.
Third Party Web Sites
Domestically Speaking contains links to third-party Web sites not owned or controlled by
Domestically Speaking. Domestically Speaking is not responsible for the privacy practices or the
content of such third-party Web sites. Inclusion of any linked Web site on Domestically Speaking
does not imply or express an approval or endorsement of the linked Web site by us, or of any of
the content, opinions, products or services provided on these Web sites. Even if an affiliation
exists between Domestically Speaking and a third-party Web site, we exercise no control over
linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection
policies and procedures. If you visit a Web site via a link from one of our Sites, we encourage
you to consult that Web site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information, and
whenever interacting with any such Web site.
Public Forums
Domestically Speaking may make chat rooms, forums, blogs, article commenting, and personal
profile pages available to users. Please remember that any such information that you may choose
to provide in these areas becomes accessible to the public, and also becomes the property of
Domestically Speaking in accordance with our Terms and Conditions, and we may use such
information in any way that we see fit. Consequently, you should exercise caution when deciding
to disclose your personal information or to upload material of any kind.
Security
Domestically Speaking has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and
alteration of the information under our control. Security of information communicated by or to
us over the Internet is of utmost concern to us; however, no data transmission over the Internet
can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that your email, like most, if not all,

unencrypted Internet communications, may potentially be accessed and viewed by other Internet
users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to us. For that reason, to protect
your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider
confidential. While we strive to protect your personal information, Domestically Speaking
cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Once we receive
your transmission, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our internal systems.
Depending on the nature of the inquiry, your communication may be discarded or archived.
Policy Regarding Minors
Children should always ask parents before providing any personal information online. No
information should be submitted to or posted on Domestically Speaking by any minor (a person
under 18 years of age) without the consent of a parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed
during collection, we do not knowingly provide any Personally Identifiable Information about
minors, regardless of its source, nor is this information knowingly used by Domestically
Speaking for any marketing or promotional purposes. Minors are not eligible to participate in
contests.
Domestically Speaking abides by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. In the event that
we learn that we have collected information from any child under the age of 13 without
verification of parental consent, we will delete this information from our database as quickly as
reasonably possible. If you believe that any Site has collected any information about anyone
under 13, please contact Domestically Speaking’s Site Administrator via postal mail or email at
one of the addresses listed below.
Financial Relationships
Please note that Domestically Speaking may have financial relationships with some of the
merchants/vendors mentioned on this website. In some instances, Domestically Speaking may be
compensated if consumers choose to utilize the links located throughout the content on this site
and generate sales for said merchant/vendor.
Limitation of Liability
Domestically Speaking PROVIDES THE INFORMATION, SERVICES AND PRODUCTS ON
THIS WEB SITES “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. YOU AGREE THAT
Domestically Speaking SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT FOUND ON
OUR FORUMS THAT ANY DOWNLOADING OF MATERIALS FOUND ON OR
THROUGH Domestically Speaking FORUMS IS DONE AT YOUR OWN RISK, AND THAT
Domestically Speaking IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR UNSOLICITED COMMUNICATIONS
THAT ARISE FROM YOUR POSTINGS. Domestically Speaking SHALL NOT BE
RESPONSIBLE IN ANY MANNER FOR THE ACTS OF ANY THIRD PARTY, INCLUDING
WITOUT LIMITATION, ANY THIRD PARTY AD NETWORK.
Consent and Modifications to this Privacy Statement
Domestically Speaking is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States.
By using Domestically Speaking and/or participating in the activities of Domestically Speaking
Community, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Statement. If you do not
agree with this Privacy Statement, please do not disclose any personal information through our
site. Domestically Speaking may modify this Privacy Statement at any time, at its discretion, and

modifications are effective upon being posted on this the applicable Site. You are responsible for
reviewing this Privacy Statement periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.
This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 2013 and supersedes all earlier versions of our
Privacy Policy
